<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyNaav</string>
    <string-array name="BoatStand">
        <item>Boat Stand</item>
        <item>Assi Ghat</item>
        <item>Raj Ghat</item>
        <item>Ahilya Ghat</item>
        <item>Chet Ghat</item>
        <item>Kedar Ghat</item>
        <item>Tulsi Ghat</item>
        <item>Bhadaini Ghat</item>
        <item>Janki Ghat</item>
        <item>Prabhu Ghat</item>
        <item>Dashashwamedh Ghat</item>
        <item>Manikarnika Ghat</item>
        <item>Ramnagar Fort and Ghat</item>
        <item>Others</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Gender">
        <item>Gender</item>
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Others</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="BoatSize">
        <item>Boat Size</item>
        <item>Small</item>
        <item>Medium</item>
        <item>Large</item>
        <item>Others</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_bottonnav">bottonnav</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="TnC_full">

        <p> <b><h1><br></br> <br></br>         TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USERS</h1></b>

Please read the Terms of Use carefully before using the Platform or registering on the Platform or accessing any material or information through the Platform.<br></br> <br></br>

Use of and access to the Platform is offered to You upon the condition of
acceptance of all the terms, conditions, and notices contained in this Terms of
Use and Privacy Policy, along with any amendments made by the Company at
its sole discretion and posted on the Platform from time to time. </p>
        <br></br>
<b>1. SERVICES</b><br></br><br></br>
<p>The Platform provides the following services to You:</p>
        <br></br>
<p>1. It allows you to avail riding services provided by the Pilot on our Platform
    (MyNaav).</p>
        <br></br>
        <br></br>
<b>2. GENERAL TERMS OF USE</b>
<p>
    1. You must be at least 18 years of age, or the age of legal majority in your
jurisdiction (if different than 18 years), to obtain an account.<br></br>

    2. If the Company becomes aware, or it acquires credible knowledge that You
have misled us regarding your age, then the Company reserves its rights to
deactivate the account and You will not be liable to raise any claims including
any insurance from the Company.<br></br>

    3. The Company will take your booking request and forward it to the Pilot
through a web and app-based device operating on GPS-GPRS based device
available with the Pilot.<br></br>

    4. The Company may monitor and record calls made to the Pilot, for the purpose
of training and improving customer care services, including complaint.

    5. The Pilot will have the sole discretion to accept or reject each request for the
Service. <br></br>

    6. If the Pilot accepts the booking request made by the Company, a notification
will be sent you with the information regarding the Pilot including its name,
contact number etc.<br></br>

    7. The Company will make reasonable efforts to bring you in contact with the
Pilot in order to obtain the Service subject to availability of the Pilot in or
around your location at the time of your booking request made to the
Company.<br></br>

    8. For the avoidance of doubt, it is clarified that the Company itself does not
provide the Services. It is the Pilot who will render the Services to you.Even
after acceptance of booking, the Pilot may not reach your pick-up location or
decide not to render his services. in which event the Company will not be held
liable.<br></br>

    9. You warrant that the information you provide to the Company is accurate and
complete. The Company is entitled at all times to verify the information that
you have provided. You may only access the Services using authorized
means.<br></br>

    10. The Company will not be liable if you do not download the correct
Platform or visit the appropriate web portal.<br></br>

    11. The Company reserves the right to discontinue or introduce any of the
modes of booking Boats.<br></br>

    12. You will refrain from doing anything which we reasonably believe to be
disreputable or capable of damaging our reputation and will comply with all
applicable laws of the Republic of India.<br></br>

    13. You will treat the Pilot with respect and not cause damage to their Boat
or engage in any unlawful, threatening, harassing, abusive behaviour or
activity whilst using their Boat;<br></br>

    14. The Company is not responsible for the behaviour, actions or inactions
of Pilots of Boats, Pilot or quality of Boat which you may use. Any contract for
the provision of Boat for the Services is exclusively between you and the Pilot
and the Company is not a party to the same.<br></br><br></br>
By using the Platform of the Company, you further agree
that:<br></br><br></br>

    14. You will download the web or Application for your sole, personal use
and will not resell it to a third party;<br></br>

    15. You will not authorize others to use your account;<br></br>

    16. You will not assign or otherwise transfer your account to any other
person or legal entity;<br></br>

    17. You will not use the Application for unlawful purposes, including but not
limited to sending or storing any unlawful material or for fraudulent purposes;<br></br>

    18. You will not use the Application to cause nuisance, annoyance or
inconvenience;<br></br>

    19. You will not impair the proper operation of the network;<br></br>

    20. You will not try to harm the Application in any way whatsoever;<br></br>

    21. You will not copy, or distribute the Application or other Company
Content without written permission from the Company;<br></br>

    22. You will keep secure and confidential your account password or any
identification which the Company may provide you which allows access to the
Application;<br></br>

    23. You will provide the Company with whatever proof of identity we may
request;<br></br>

    24. In order for us to facilitate UPI payments, we are required to conduct a
bank account validation and Virtual Payment Address (“VPA”) validation. We
conduct these validations through a third-party service provider.<br></br>

    25. You will only use an access point or atleast a 3G data account (AP)
which you are authorized to use;<br></br>

    26. You will not use the Application with an incompatible or unauthorized
device;<br></br>

    27. If within 24 hours a user creates more than one account on the same
device, MyNaav has the right to terminate his/her account.

    28. In case of any disturbance or problems customer will provide written
complain to company first.<br></br>

    15. The Company reserves the right to immediately terminate your use of
the Application should you not comply with the any of the rules provided in the
    Terms of Use.<br></br><br></br>

    <b>3. PAYMENT FOR SERVICES</b><br></br><br></br>


    1. You will be required to pay charges for the Services used by you either by
using the online payment gateway provided in the Platform or by paying cash
to the Pilot. The Company collects the charges for the Services on behalf of
the Pilot after obtaining authorisation from the Pilot and the payment is
remitted to the Pilot’s bank account registered with the Company. . You agree
and acknowledge that MyNaav is not in any way be responsible for the
settlement between you and the Pilot.<br></br>

    2. The rates of the Services will be notified on the website and mobile application
of the Company.<br></br>

    3. The charges for the Services will be updated or amended from time to time at
the sole discretion of the Company and it will be your responsibility to remain
informed about the charges for the Services.

    4. You agree that you will pay for all Services to the Pilot either by way of online
payment or by cash. In the event the payment cannot be accepted through the
online payment or any other mode, you will be required to pay the charges for
the Services availed by way of cash.<br></br>

    5. Any payment made is non-refundable. At the end of the trip for the
Transportation Services, we will facilitate for you to receive a copy of the
invoice from the Company on your registered e-mail account with the
Company.<br></br>

    6. It is clarified that the term “Trip” includes a trip for transportation of a
passenger by the Pilot.<br></br><br></br>

    <b>4. LIABILITY</b><br></br><br></br>


    1. The information, recommendations provided to you on or through the website,
or the Platform is for general information purposes only and does not
constitute advice.<br></br>

    2. The Company will reasonably keep the website and the application and its
contents correct and up to date but does not guarantee that the website
and/or application are free of errors, defects, malware and viruses or that the
website and/or application are correct, up to date and accurate. The Company
will not be liable for any damage arising from the same.<br></br>

    3. The Company will further not be liable for damages resulting from the use of
or the inability to use the website or the application, including – but not limited
to – damages resulting from failure or delay in delivery of electronic
communications, interception or manipulation of electronic communications by
third parties or by computer programs used for electronic communications and
transmission of viruses.<br></br>

    4. The quality of the Services requested through the use of the Platform is
entirely the responsibility of the Pilot who ultimately provides such Services to
you and the Company is not liable for the same. However, any complaints
about the Services provided by the Pilot should be submitted to the Company
by an email as notified from time to time.<br></br><br></br>

    <b>5. INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS</b><br></br><br></br>


    1. The Company is the sole owner and lawful licensee of all the rights to the web
site, Platform or any other digital media and its contents. The content means
its Design, layout, text, images, graphics, sounds, video, etc. the website,
Platform or any other digital media content embody trade secrets and
intellectual property rights protected under worldwide copyright and other
laws. All titles, ownership and intellectual property rights in the website and its
content will remain with the Company, its affiliates, agents, authorized
representatives or licensor’s as the case may be.<br></br>

    2. All rights not otherwise claimed under this Terms of Use or by the Company
are hereby reserved. The information contained in this Platform and/or
website is intended, solely to provide general information for the personal use
of the reader, who accepts full responsibility for its use.<br></br>

    3. The Company does not represent or endorse the accuracy or reliability of any
information or advertisement contained on, distributed through, or linked,
downloaded or accessed from any of the services contained on this website or
Platform, or the quality of any products, information or other materials
displayed, or obtained by you as a result of any product, information or other
materials displayed, or obtained by you as a result of an advertisement or any
other information or offer in or in connection with the service.<br></br>

    4. All related icons and logos are registered trademarks or service marks or word
marks of the Company in various jurisdictions and are protected under
applicable copyrights, trademarks and other proprietary rights laws. The
unauthorized copying, modification, use or publication of these marks is
strictly prohibited.<br></br>

    5. All the contents on this website and/or Platform is copyright of the Company
except the third-party content and link to third party website on our website
and/or Platform.<br></br>

    6. Subject to your compliance with these Terms, the Company grants you a
limited non-exclusive, non-transferable license to download and install a copy
of the Platform on a single mobile device that you own or control and to run
such copy of the Platform solely for your own personal use.<br></br>
You will not do the following:<br></br>
License, sublicense, sell, resell, transfer, assign, distribute or otherwise
commercially exploit or make available to any third party the Platform in any
way;<br></br>

    Modify or make derivative works based upon the Platform;<br></br>

    Create Internet “links” or “frame” or “mirror” any application on any other
server or wireless or Internet-based device<br></br>
Reverse engineer or access the Platform in order to design or build a
competitive product or service,<br></br>

    Design or build a product using similar ideas, features, functions, or graphics
of the Platform, or copy any ideas, features, functions or graphics of the
Platform, or launch a mated program or script, including, but not limited to,
web spiders, web crawlers, web robots, web ants, web indexers, bots, viruses
or worms, or any program which may make multiple server requests per
second, or unduly burdens or hinders the operation and/or performance of the
Platform.<br></br><br></br>

    <b>6. THIRD-PARTY LINKS</b><br></br><br></br>

    1. During the use of the website or the application, links to websites that are
owned and controlled by third parties may be provided from time to time in
order to enter into correspondence with, participate in promotions of third
parties. These links take you off the website, the application and are beyond
the Company’s control.<br></br>

    2. During use of the website and the application, you may enter into
correspondence with, or participate in promotions of third-party Pilot,
advertisers or sponsors showing their services through a link on the website or
through the application or Service. These links take you off the website, the
application and the Service and are beyond the Company’s control. You
therefore visit or access these websites entirely at your own risk.<br></br>

    3. Please note that these other websites may send their own cookies to users,
collect data or solicit personal information, and you are therefore advised to
check the Terms of use or privacy policies on those websites prior to using
them.<br></br><br></br>

    <b>7. TERM AND TERMINATION</b> <br></br><br></br>


    1. The contract between the Company and you is concluded for an indefinite
period. You are entitled to terminate the Contract at all times by permanent
deletion of the Platform installed on your mobile device, tablet or any
electronic device capable of using the Platform thus disabling the use by you
of the Platform and the Service.<br></br>

    2. The Company is entitled to terminate the contract at all times and with
immediate effect (by disabling your use of the application and the Service) if
you: violate or breach any term of these Terms of Use, or in the opinion of the
Company, misuse of the Platform or the Service.<br></br>

    3. The Company is not obliged to give notice of the termination of the contract in
advance. After termination the Company will give notice thereof in accordance
with these Terms of Use.<br></br>

    4. Neither party hereto will be responsible for delays or failures in performance
resulting from acts beyond its reasonable control and without its fault or
negligence. Such excusable delays or failures may be caused by, among
other things, strikes, lock-out, riots, rebellions, accidental explosions, floods,
storms, acts of God and similar occurrences.<br></br><br></br>

    <b>8. INDEMNITY</b> <br></br><br></br>


    You will indemnify and hold the Company harmless, from any and all claims,
losses, liabilities, damages, expenses, and costs (including attorneys’ fees
and court costs) which result from a breach or alleged breach of these Terms
of Use by you.<br></br>

    <b>9. ASSIGNMENT</b><br></br><br></br>


    You may not assign your rights under these Terms of Use without the prior
written approval of the Company.<br></br>

    <b>10. AMENDMENT</b>


    <br></br>These Terms of Use may be amended from time to time and as and when
required, at the discretion of the Company.<br></br><br></br>

    <b>11. SEVERABILITY</b>


    <br></br>If any provision or any part of a provision of these Terms of Use is invalid,
unenforceable, or prohibited by applicable laws of the Republic of India, such
provision or part or the provision will be severed from these Terms of Use and
will be considered divisible as to such provision or part thereof and such
provision or part thereof will be inoperative and will not be part of the
consideration moving between you and the Company hereto and the
remainder of these Terms of Use will be valid and binding and of like effect as
though such provision was not included herein.<br></br><br></br>

    <b>12. NOTICES</b><br></br>


    The Company may give notice by means of a general notice physically or on
the website and Application, or by electronic mail to your email address on
record in the Company’s account information, or by written communication
sent by regular mail to your address on record in Company’s account
information.<br></br><br></br>
        </p>
    </string>
    <string name="TnC1">
        <p><b>                 Boat-Pilot’s Terms and Conditions</b>


On the basis of the representations and warranties provided by the Pilot, the
Company has agreed to list the boat on the Portal to enable the Pilot to
provide the Services through the Portal in accordance with the terms and
conditions as hereinafter provided (“T&amp;Cs“).
1. GENERAL COVENANTS

1. The Company will take the booking request and forward it to the Pilot through
a web &amp; app-based device operating on GPS-GPRS based device.
2. The Company reserves the right to discontinue or introduce any of the modes
of booking boats.
3. The Pilot will have the rights to accept or reject each request for the Service.
4. The Pilot warrants that the information it provides to the Company is accurate
and complete. The Company is entitled at all times to verify the information
that has been provided.
5. The Pilot will refrain from doing anything which the Company reasonably
believes to be disreputable or capable of damaging the Company’s reputation
and will comply with all applicable laws of the Republic of India.
6. In relation to the Portal, the Pilot agrees to:
1. Not authorize others to use his account on the Portal;
2. Not assign or otherwise transfer his account to any other person or legal
entity;
3. Not use the Portal for unlawful purposes, including but not limited to sending
or storing any unlawful material or for fraudulent purposes;
4. not use the Portal to cause nuisance, annoyance or inconvenience;
5. Not impair the proper operation of the network;
6. Not try to harm the Portal in any way;
7. Not copy, or distribute any content on the Portal without written permission
from the Company;
8. keep secure and confidential the account password or any identification which
the Company may provide to the Pilot which allows access to the Portal;
9. Provide the Company with whatever proof of identity the Company may
request.
7. The Company reserves the right to immediately terminate the use of the Portal
by the Pilot if he does not comply any term and conditions.
 Rate would be fixed and only change by the company’s requirements.
 Number of Customers would be fix.
 Surety to complete the bookings on time.
 Complete the booking rides.
 Company will provide full support and assistance to the Boat owners for better
Customer Experience.
 Company will take 10% to 20% money from the profit and 10% to 20% will
give to the boat owners.
 Contract will be change or update only by company‘s requirements.
 Boat owners cannot break the contract without informing us.
Note- Boat owners will have to obey and fulfil all the company’s terms and
conditions.

2. PAYMENT TERMS

1. The Company has the discretion to charge any such fees from the Pilot as
updated on the Portal from time to time.
2. The Company charges a convenience fee from the commuters for providing
the Services through the Pilots. Further, the Pilot authorizes the Company to
collect the service/travel fee (“Fare”) from the users on behalf of the Pilots.
3. If the Fare is collected in cash by the Pilot it will get adjusted against the
convenience fee.

3. REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES

The Pilot and the Company represent that:
1. They have all requisite power and authority to, deliver and perform the
obligations imposed herein;
2. The execution and performance of the obligations do not and will not violate
any provision of any existing agreement, law, rule, regulation, any order or
judicial pronouncement which is applicable to each party;
3. They have not been convicted by any court in India or any other country of
any crimes including but not limited to involving moral turpitude.
The Pilot hereby represents that:
1. he has the requisite authority or assignment to ride the Boat and there are no
restrictions with respect to the use of the Boat that will hinder the Rider from
the performance of the Services using the Portal;
2. he has all rights, licenses, and permits as may be required under applicable
laws to perform the Service in accordance with these T&amp;Cs
            3. he will hold and keep updated/renewed licenses, insurance and permits
necessary for the use of Boat.
4. he will not ride rashly, will follow rules &amp; regulations and all applicable laws
during the performance of the Services, not consume liquor/cigarette/bidi, or
any other kind of intoxicant while performing the Services and will have and
hold a valid riding license and registration/insurance papers for the Boat at all
times. The Pilot will not take any personal calls except in the event of an
emergency, without prejudicing the safety of the Boat and the customer. The
Pilot will take all calls from the customer and the Company only after stopping
the Boat at an appropriate location to take the call. he will provide the services
in a courteous and professional manner as reasonably expected by a service
provider providing the Services.
5. He will at all times during which he is undertaking the Services, maintain
dress, appearance, and hygiene codes.
6. He will perform its obligations with promptness and use reasonable care and
skill and in accordance with standards of diligence, care, skill, quality and
integrity to be reasonably expected of an experienced and reputable provider
of Services;
7. He will perform each pick-up and delivery in the most efficient manner
possible and will make best efforts to adhere to the timelines prescribed.
8. He will also ensure the safety of packages is not compromised at the time of
delivery.
9. He will not consume any alcoholic beverages or any other intoxicating/banned
substances prior to or during the performance of the Services.

4. RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN THE PARTIES

1. Independent Contractor: The Pilot will operate as and have the status of an
independent contractor. The relationship between the Company and the Pilot
is on a principal-to-principal basis. The Company and the Pilot are
independent legal entities, and nothing in these T&amp;Cs will be construed to
create a partnership, joint venture, an association of persons, agency
(disclosed or undisclosed), franchise, sales representative, or employment
relationship between the Company and the Pilot. It is clarified that the Pilot will
not have any right to conclude any contract for and / or on the behalf of the
Company.

5. PILOT INFORMATION

1. Vboat may collect Pilot Information at the time of onboarding of the Pilots, to
establish the identity of the Pilots. Vboat reserves the right to store, process,
access and use the Pilot Information for business purposes and needs,
background check, verification, marketing, service, development, analytics,
research, and any other purpose as Vboat may deem fit and in accordance
with Applicable Law. The Pilot hereby expressly consents to such collection
and use of Pilot Information.
2. Subject to applicable laws, Vboat may provide to a third party, governmental
agency, judicial body, any Pilot Information or information relating to the Pilot,
if there is a complaint, dispute or conflict, including any accident involving a
Pilot on one hand and end-consumer, or a third party on the other hand;
3. “Pilot Information” will mean and include any personal data collected from
the Pilot including know your customer documents with Pilot’s bank, copies of
valid government-issued boat registration certificate, mobile number, bank
account details, boat insurance copy, driving license, identity proof, residence
proof, location data, proof of ownership of Pilots’ Boat and any other
information that Vboat may deem fit.

6. CONFIDENTIALITY

1. The Pilot will keep confidential all data including customer details, market
information, all work products and documents related thereto, the contents of
the Portal and will not sell or otherwise make that information available to any
third parties. Except as otherwise agreed, the data of customers will be the
exclusive property of the Company, and the Pilot will not use the same for any
purpose or distribute such data in any form or means except for the purpose
of providing the Services and other than as permitted by the Company and will
keep it confidential at all times.
2. The Pilot agrees to indemnify, defend and hold the Company harmless from
and against any claim, liability, obligation, loss, damage, deficiency,
assessment, judgment, cost or expense (including, without limitation to costs
and expenses incurred in preparing and defending against or prosecuting any
litigation, claim, action, suit proceeding or demand) of any kind or character,
arising out of or in any manner incidental, relating, or attributable to any
inaccuracy, breach, or failure by the Pilot to perform its obligations under
these T&amp;Cs or the applicable laws in relation to performance of the Services.

8. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

1. The Company is not liable to the Pilot, for any condition, suitability, quality,
merchantability and fitness for any purposes in respect of the Portal or the
services provided through the Portal and is not liable for any civil, criminal,
tortious, or any other liability, that may accrue as a consequence of the use
and access of the Portal.
2. To the extent permissible under applicable laws, the Company is not liable for
any civil, criminal, tortious, or any other liability, that may accrue as a
consequence of the breach by the Service Provider of the applicable laws in
respect of the use of the Portal or providing the Services; of the terms of the
applicable licenses and permits that are issued by the authorities; of the terms
of these T&amp;Cs or of the duty of care the Pilot owes to the users of the Portals.
3. The Company is not responsible for the behaviour, actions or inactions of the
Pilot, quality of the Boat. Any contract for the provision of Boat is exclusively
between the customer and the Pilot and the Company is not a party to the
same.
4. All rights not otherwise claimed under these T&amp;Cs or by the Company are
hereby reserved. The information contained in this Portal is intended, solely to
provide general information for the personal use of the reader, who accepts
full responsibility for its use.
5. The Company does not represent or endorse the accuracy or reliability of any
information or advertisement contained on, distributed through, or linked,
downloaded or accessed from any of the services contained on the Portal, or
the quality of any products, information or other materials displayed, or
obtained by you as a result of any product, information or other materials
displayed, or obtained by you as a result of an advertisement or any other
information or offer in or in connection with the service.
6. The Pilot will not do the following:
1. license, sublicense, sell, resell, transfer, assign, distribute or otherwise
commercially exploit or make available to any third party the Portal in any way;
2. modify or make derivative works based upon the Portal;
3. Reverse engineer or access the Portal in order to design or build a
competitive product or service,
4. Design or build a product using similar ideas, features, functions or graphics of
the Portal, or copy any ideas, features, functions or graphics of the Portal, or
launch an automated program or script, including, but not limited to, web
spiders, web crawlers, web robots, web ants, web indexers, bots, viruses or
worms, or any program which may make multiple server requests per second,
or unduly burdens or hinders the operation and/or performance of the Portal.

9. TERM AND TERMINATION

Company is entitled to terminate the contract at all times and with immediate
effect (by disabling the Pilot’s registration on the Portal and use of the Portal)
for:
1. Any violation or breach of any term of these T&amp;Cs or If the Pilot, in the
opinion of the Company, misuses the Portal and failure to verify or
authenticate Pilot Information;
1. Any action or omission by the Pilot which can cause legal or contractual
liability for Vboat including but not limited to fraudulent conduct, customer
complaints, continuous unsatisfactory reviews by the Restaurant Partners or
the Users, misconduct, negligence, and all other actions specifically prohibited
under Applicable Law.
2. Vboat is also at liberty to terminate the contract at their discretion, where, in
their opinion, continuance of the services of Pilot is detrimental to the business
interest of Vboat due to the acts of the Pilots, such as the following:
1. Misbehavior, rude behavior with the staff of Vboat, customers or any other
persons associated with the Vboat.
2. Any acts involving criminal offence punishable under law, including physical
assault, threatening any of the staff of Vboat, person associated with Vboat
and any other persons.
3. Concealment of fact/material information while entering into a contract with
Vboat.
4. Poor &amp; irregular for work, meetings and failure to abide by the rules/terms of
the contract.
5. Drunk while on duty and drunken behavior.
6. Commission of fraud/ misappropriation/embezzlement for undue monetary
gain, which is against the interest of the Vboat.
7. Negligence in performing the duty, causing damage of moveable and
immoveable assets of Vboat, its employees, customers.
8. Indulging in spreading content through digital media, social networking sites,
or any other form, which could be detrimental to Vboat’s brand and its image.
9. Indulging in acts such as creating ruckus/ strike/ or any activity against Vboat,
which could be detrimental to the Vboat’s brand and its image.
10. Indulging in unauthorized disclosure of confidential information of Vboat
to external agency, person, Vboat or organization.
11. Misuse of assets provided by Vboat and welcome kits, which could be
detrimental to the interest of Vboat’s brand and its image.
12. Absconding for more than 4 hours with any asset, delivery item, money
or any other valuable item belonging to Vboat, its employees, customers or
other staff member(s).
13. Failure to abide by any of the rules and guidelines given by Vboat as
part of service quality standards and principles.
14. Doing any act unbecoming of a Pilot.
15. In case the background check, whether wholly or partially, is found
negative at any point of time during the term of these T&amp;Cs.
The Company is not obliged to give notice of the termination of the contract in
advance.

10. ASSIGNMENT

The Pilot may not assign its rights or obligations under these T&amp;Cs without
prior written approval of the Company.

11. AMENDMENT

These T&amp;Cs may be amended from time to time and as and when required, at
the discretion of the Company.

12. SEVERABILITY

If any provision or any part of a provision of these T&amp;Cs is invalid,
unenforceable or prohibited by applicable laws of the Republic of India , such
provision or part of provision will be severed from these T&amp;Cs and will be
considered divisible as to such provision or part thereof and such provision or
part thereof will be inoperative and will not be part of the consideration moving
between you and the Company hereto and the remainder of these T&amp;Cs will
be valid and binding and of like effect as though such provision was not
included herein.

13. INSURANCE

The Company at its sole discretion may insure the Pilot against any accident
suffered by the Pilot during provision of Services by the Pilot using the Portal.
The Company reserves the right to recover any amount paid by the Company
in lieu of the insurance from the Pilot.

14. NOTICES

1. The Company may give notice by means of a general notice on the Portal, or
by electronic mail to your email address on record in the Company’s account
information, or by written communication sent by regular mail to the Pilot’s
address on record in the Company’s account information.
2. Pilot needs to send any notice on at email id:info@mynaav.com
        </p>
    </string>
</resources>